Division of Invertebrate Paleontology Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
Division of Invertebrate Paleontology Archives
1861-2014
IPAR.001260
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
25
The archives of Division of Invertebrate Paleontology.
Division of Invertebrate Paleontology, Yale Peabody Museum
Biographical Sketch
The Yale Peabody Museum?s collection of invertebrate fossils is one of largest in the United States, in volume and in geographic, stratigraphic and taxonomic representation. The holdings of the Division of Invertebrate Paleontology represent more than 350,000 specimen lots, approximately 4 million individuals. A total of 35,000 are type specimens; about 4,500 are the basis of new species descriptions. Over 300,000 specimen lots are available in the online specimen index; all known type specimens are included.
Strengths of the collections include Early Paleozoic faunas from Maritime Canada and the Appalachians, Late Paleozoic faunas from the Mid-Continent and Western North America, and Mesozoic mollusks from the western interior of the United States. Among the Division?s notable collections are:
The Schuchert Collection of brachiopods, which includes the collections of Fred Braun, W.H. Twenhofeland Darling K. Greger (to name a few)
Trilobites from the Beecher?s Bed Lagerstatten.
The June R. P. Ross Collection of bryozoa.
The Charles A. Ross Collection of fusilinida.
Historical collections from Anticosti Island, Canada (collected by W.H. Twenhofel and Charles Schuchert)
Several large collections of Devonian brachiopods and mollusks from New York State and the central United States (collected by Thayer, Bambach and others).
Description of the Material
Includes a number of geologic maps (USA - Arizona, Colorado, Ohio, New Mexico, New York, Texas, Utah; Canada - Nova Scotia; India; South America), topographic maps (USA - California, Connecticut, Illinois, Kansas, Kentucky, Maine, Maryland, Missouri, Nevada, New Jersey, New Mexico, New York, Ohio, Pennsylvania, South Dakota, Texas, Vermont, Virginia, West Virginia, Wyoming; Canada - Nova Scotia, Quebec; India; Peru), and other maps (USA - Connecticut, Florida, Nebraska, New Mexico, Texas, Utah; Canada - Quebec; Ghana; Saudi Arabia; Sweden - Gotland; Venezuela). Also includes locality information from unpublished and published locality registers and dissertations. Also includes photographs and slides of specimens, localities, and people (including J. E. Harding, GSA Fellows from 1889-1899, Charles Schuchert, Carl Dunbar, Giorgio Panella, Ed Leith, J. Brookes Knight, Russell Logie, G. Arthur Cooper, Percy Morris, Arthur Miller, Norman Newell, Chester Longwell, Berlen Moneymaker, Richard Lull, Perry Wilson, Adolph Knopf, George Lewis, and Richard Foster Flint). Also, field notebooks, specimen information, divisional correspondence, and other miscellaneous material.
Yale Peabody Museum; Yale University
- Maps, Series I
  - Africa., 001270
    - Location map. 2 locality maps for Devonian of Ghana, Africa., 1961; 000364
  - Canada., 001269
    - Geologic map. Graham Island (1: 126720). U.S. Geological Survey: Geologic., 1916; 001589
    - Geologic map. St. Elie D'Orford Area (1: 12000). U.S. Geological Survey: Geologic., 1963; 001593
    - Geologic map. Arisaig, Nova Scotia (1: 600). U.S. Geological Survey: Geologic., 1969; 001850
    - Geologic map. Arisaig, Nova Scotia (1: 6000). U.S. Geological Survey: Geologic., 1969; 001853
    - Geologic map. U.S. Dept of Agriculture, base (1: 31680). U.S. Geological Survey: Geologic., 001858
    - Highway map. Le Quebec a la Carte (1: 500000). Dept. Mines & Technical Survey [Quebec]: Highway., 1981; 001915
    - Map. Stephenville, NF Quad. (1: 250,000), Sheet 12B Surveys and Mabbing Branch, Dept. of Mines and Technical Surveys, Canada, 1959; 002227
    - Topographic map. Port-Menier, Quebec, 22H (1: 250000). Dept. Mines & Technical Survey [Quebec]: Topographic., 1959; 001861
    - Topographic map. Gaspe, Quebec, 22A (1: 250000). Dept. Mines & Technical Survey [Quebec]: Topographic., 1959; 001862
    - Topographic map. Arisaig, Nova Scotia (1: 600). U.S. Geological Survey: Geologic., 1969; 001851
    - Topographic map. Arisaig, Nova Scotia (1: 600). U.S. Geological Survey: Geologic., 1969; 001852
    - Topographic map. Arisaig, Nova Scotia (1: 50000). U.S. Geological Survey: Geologic., 1969; 001854
    - Topographic map. Arisaig, Nova Scotia (1: 600). U.S. Geological Survey: Geologic., 1969; 001855
    - Topographic map. Grondines, 31 1/9 East (1: 50000). Dept. Mines & Technical Survey [Quebec]: Topographic., 1971; 001916
    - Topographic map. Portneuf, 21 L\12 W (1: 50000). Dept. Mines & Technical Survey [Quebec]: Topographic., 1971; 001917
    - Topographic map. Aston, 31-I/1 (1: 50000). Dept. Mines & Technical Survey [Quebec]: Topographic., 1971; 001919
    - Topographic map. Yamaska, 31-1/2 (1: 50000). Dept. Mines & Technical Survey [Quebec]: Topographic., 1980; 001918
    - Map: DUNVILLE, ONTARIO, CANADA. Department of National Defence, Army Service Establishment (ASE). SHEET 30L/13 WEST HALF.Third edition, revised 1952. Scale 1:50,000. Contour Interval 25 feet., 002709
    - Map: Canada Mines and Technichal Surveys, Surveys and Mapping branch, First Edition. CANADA, SHEET 30 L/15 WEST HALF. FORT ERIE-NEW YORK. Scale 1:50,000, 1.25 inches to 1 Mile approximately. Contour interval 25 feet., 1955; 002708
  - India., 001271
    - Geologic map. Geology of Malaya (1: 63420). U.S. Geological Survey: Geologic., 1930; 001620
    - Topographic map. Punjab, India, Topographic Map (1:63360), Map no. 43 H/5, Survey of India: Topographic, 1910; 002295
    - Topographic map. Attock, Mianwali & Shahpur Districts (1: 63630). Survey of India: Topographic., 1911; 001628
    - Topographic map. Mianwali & Shahpur Districts (1: 63630). Survey of India: Topographic., 1911; 001629
    - Topographic map. Punjab, Second edition, Topographic Map (1:63360), Map no. 43 H/1, Survey of India: Topographic, 1911; 002294
    - Topographic map. Mianwall, Attock & Shahpur Districts (1: 31680). Survey of India: Topographic., 1913; 001632
    - Topographic map. Baramula & Muzaffarabad Districts (1: 63630). Survey of India: Topographic., 1914; 001630
    - Topographic map. Yu Nan Province (1: 253440). Survey of India: Topographic., 1917; 001631
    - Topographic map. Kashmir & Jammu & Punjab, Second Edition (1927), Topographic Map (1:253440), Map no. 43 H, Survey of India: Topographic, 002293
  - Miscellaneous., 001275
    - Location map. Reeds' District A of unpub. Yale Dissertation (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1910; 001622
    - Location map. Reeds' District B of unpub. Yale Dissertation (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1910; 001623
    - Location map. Reeds' District D of unpub. Yale Dissertation (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1910; 001625
    - Location map. Reed's District E of unpub. Yale Dissertation (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1910; 001626
    - Topographic map. Reeds' District C of unpub. Yale Dissertation (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1910; 001624
  - Saudi Arabia., 001272
    - Location map. Location map of fossil localities: Saudi Arabia., 1986; 000167
  - South America., 001274
    - Geologic map. Carte Geologique de L'Amerique du Sud: (1: 5000000). Commission de la Carte Geologic du Monde. [South America], 1964; 002195
    - Location map. 2 locality maps: Venezuela., 1934; 000373
    - Topographic map. Photocopy of Little's maps & notes (photocopy of recent topographic & geologic maps): Peru., 1922; 000277
  - Sweden., 001273
    - Highway map. Gotland, Sweden 1:300,000, 002287
  - USA., 001268
    - Dissertation. Deep Creek, UT 15 Quad. (1: 62500). dissertation: Geologic., 1958; 002114
    - Geologic map. A Geological and Topographical Map of most of Bucks and Montgomery Counties [PA]: West Sheet: (1: 63360). Geological Survey of Pennsylvania: (by Lyman, B.S., 1893)., 1896; 002065
    - Geologic map. A Geological and Topographical Map of most of Bucks and Montgomery Counties [PA]: East Sheet: (1: 63360). Geological Survey of Pennsylvania: (by Lyman, B.S., 1893)., 1896; 002066
    - Geologic map. A Geological and Topographical Map of most of Bucks and Montgomery Counties [PA]: East Sheet: (1: 63360). Geological Survey of Pennsylvania: (by Lyman, B.S., 1893)., 1896; 002067
    - Geologic map. A Geological and Topographical Map of most of Bucks and Montgomery Counties [PA]: West Sheet: (1: 63360). Geological Survey of Pennsylvania: (by Lyman, B.S., 1893)., 1896; 002068
    - Geologic map. Geologic Map of Ohio. Scale 1:500000. Geological Survey of Ohio, compiled by J. A. Bownocker., 1947; 002419
    - Geologic map. Escalante-Boulder Area (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Geological., 1956; 001868
    - Geologic map. New York State (1: 250000). N.Y. State Geological Survey: Geologic &Topographic, 1961; 001439
    - Geologic map. Geologic map of Hueco Mountains, Texas-New Mexico (1: 31680 approximatly). dissertation composite., 1962; 002113
    - Geologic map. U.S. Dept. of Agriculture, base (1: 31680). U.S. Geological Survey: Geologic., 001859
    - Geologic map. U.S. Dept. of Agriculture, base (1: 31680). U.S. Geological Survey: Geologic., 001860
    - Geologic map. Portal, AR-NM 15 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 001920
    - Geologic map. Chiricahua Mt.; Geol. Soc. Am. Bull. 68, 1957 (1: 62500). Geological Society of America: Geologic., 001921
    - Geologic map. Treasure Mt. Dome (1: 10000). U.S. Geological Survey: Geologic., 001942
    - Highway map. Sarasota [Florida] Metro, FL (1: 1761). Rand McNally: Highway., 1988; 001621
    - Location map. Photocopy of map of Nebraska Territory, by Lt. G.K. Warren: Western Interior of United States., 1855; 000303
    - Location map. Oyster Grounds, West Haven, New Haven, East Haven, Branford, [lease map, revision of Feb. 16, 1998]. (1: 24000). Connecticut Department of Agriculture (Aquaculture Division): Nauutical Chart., 002212
    - Location map. Locality information including maps, photographs, 35 mm slides, & partial photocopy of the Marjum Pass, Utah 7.5 Quad. with the 7 localities visited with Val & Lloyd Gunther, Terry Abbott and Tom & Brian Whitely., 2000; 000731
    - Map. maps of geographic area, not localities: Texas; New Mexico. 1935-1936, 000396
    - Map. Silurian & Devonian Rocks of New York State, New York State Museum: Education Series, 1975; 001428
    - Nautical chart. Long Island Sound: Eastern Part (1: 80000). Buzas, M.A.: Coastal., 1960; 001597
    - Topographic map. Pottsville, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1891 (1924), 002049
    - Topographic map. Deleware Watergap, PA-NJ 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1893 (1930), 002053
    - Topographic map. Hazleton, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1893 (1910), 002058
    - Topographic map. Wallpack, PA-NJ 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1893 (1898), 002059
    - Topographic map. Allentown, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1894 (1928), 002052
    - Topographic map. Staunton Folio, VA-WV (1: 125000); Folio 14, 1894; 002299
    - Topographic map. Willsboro, NY-VT 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1895 (1911), 002064
    - Topographic map. Franklin Folio, WV-VA (1: 125000); Folio 32, 1896; 002297
    - Topographic map. Pocahontas Folio, WV-VA (1: 125000); Folio 26, 1896; 002300
    - Topographic map. Piedmont Folio, WV-MD (1: 125000); Folio 28, 1896; 002302
    - Topographic map. Tazewell Folio, VA-WV (1: 125000); Folio 44, 1897; 002301
    - Topographic map. Harrisburg, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1899 (1929), 002046
    - Topographic map. Monterey Folio, VA-WV (1: 125000); Folio 61, 1899; 002298
    - Topographic map. Junction City, Kansas 15-min Quad, 1901; 002326
    - Topographic map. Slatington, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1902 (1924), 002051
    - Topographic map. New Milford, CT 15' Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1904; 001595
    - Topographic map. Iola, Kansas 15-min Quad, 1904; 002325
    - Topographic map. Cottonwood Falls, Kansas 15-min Quad, 1904; 002327
    - Topographic map. Ellenville, NY 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1906 (1936), 002054
    - Topographic map. Plattsburg, NY-VT 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1906 (1911), 002063
    - Topographic map. New Bloomfield, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1907 (1929), 002045
    - Topographic map. Claysville, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1907; 002057
    - Topographic map. Rouses Point, NY-VT 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1907 (1921), 002062
    - Topographic map. Las Vegas, NV 60 Quad (1: 250000) U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1907; 002284
    - Topographic map. Bellefonte, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1909 (1929), 002055
    - Topographic map. Bellefonte, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1909 (1937), 002056
    - Topographic map. Prince Frederick, MD 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1910; 001931
    - Topographic map. Hamburg, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1911 (1920), 002048
    - Topographic map. Reading, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1915 (1924), 002047
    - Topographic map. Milton, VT 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1915 (1931), 002060
    - Topographic map. St Albans, VT 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. 1916 (1931), 002061
    - Topographic map. Cape Girardeau, MO-IL 15' Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1924; 001592
    - Topographic map. Mauch Chunk, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1924; 002050
    - Topographic map. Long Pond, Maine 15-min Quad, 1924; 002322
    - Topographic map. Lewistown, PA 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1927; 002044
    - Topographic map. San Ysidro, N. Mex. 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1939; 002728
    - Topographic map. Bonner Springs, Kans.-MO. 15-min Quad, 1940; 002328
    - Topographic map. Basset Lake SW, NM-TX 15 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1943; 002165
    - Topographic map. Hueco Mountains, TX 15 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1943; 002170
    - Topographic map. Hueco Mountains, TX 15 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1943; 002171
    - Topographic map. Hueco Mountains, TX 15 Quad. (1: 31250). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1943; 002172
    - Topographic map. Hueco Mountains, TX 15 Quad. (1: 31250). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1943; 002173
    - Topographic map. Altoona, Kansas. 15-min Quad, 1943; 002329
    - Topographic map. San Ysidro, N. Mex. 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. Annotated., 1943; 002727
    - Topographic map. Hueco Tanks, TX 15 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1944; 002168
    - Topographic map. Hueco Tanks, TX 15 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1944; 002169
    - Topographic map. Buxton, ME 15-min Quad, 1944; 002307
    - Topographic map. Newburgh North, NY 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1947; 002043
    - Topographic map. Helms West Well, TX 7.5 Quad. (1 - 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. post 1947 & pre 1955, 002166
    - Topographic map. Hueco Tanks, TX 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. post 1947 & pre 1955, 002167
    - Topographic map. Jonesboro, IL-MO 15'Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1949; 001591
    - Topographic map. Jonesboro, IL-MO (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1949; 001627
    - Topographic map. Altamont, NY 7.5 Quad. (1: 25000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1949; 002039
    - Topographic map. Cobleskill, NY 7.5 Quad. (1: 25000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1949; 002040
    - Topographic map. Blanco Mountain, CA 15 min quad, 1951; 002303
    - Topographic map. Clarksville, NY 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1953; 002042
    - Topographic map. Clarlsville, NY 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1953; 002228
    - Topographic map. Livengood, AL 15 Quad. (1: 63360). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1954; 001945
    - Topographic map. Seboomook Lake, Maine 15-min Quad, 1954; 002321
    - Topographic map. Remsen, NY 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1955; 002041
    - Topographic map. Biddeford, ME 15-min Quad, 1956; 002306
    - Topographic map. Kennebunk, ME 15-min Quad, 1956; 002310
    - Topographic map. York, ME 15-min Quad, 1956; 002312
    - Topographic map. The Forks, Maine 15-min Quad, 1956; 002319
    - Topographic map. Freeport, ME 15-min Quad, 1957; 002308
    - Topographic map. Gray, ME 15-min Quad, 1957; 002309
    - Topographic map. Portland, ME 15-min Quad, 1957; 002311
    - Topographic map. Brassua Lake, Maine 15-min Quad, 1957; 002318
    - Topographic map. Moosehead Lake, Maine 15-min Quad, 1957; 002320
    - Topographic map. Black River, NY 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1958; 002038
    - Topographic map. Newcastle, WY-SD 15.0 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1958; 002276
    - Topographic map. Covington, KY - OH 7.5-min Quad, 1961; 002314
    - Topographic map. Lovell Lakes, WY 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1964; 002083
    - Topographic map. Windsor Locks, CT 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1964; 002193
    - Topographic map. Colonial Beach South, VA-MD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1968; 001927
    - Topographic map. Champlain, VA 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1968; 001928
    - Topographic map. Stratford Hall, VA-MD 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1968; 001929
    - Topographic map. Calvert County, MD 15 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1970; 001923
    - Topographic map. Frankfort West, KY 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1970; 002161
    - Topographic map. Caroline County, MD 15 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1971; 001925
    - Topographic map. Dorchester County, MD 15 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1971; 001926
    - Topographic map. St Mary's County, MD 15 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1972; 001924
    - Topographic map. Middletown, CT 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1972; 002196
    - Topographic map. Branford, CT 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1972; 002198
    - Topographic map. Broad Brook, CT 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1972; 002199
    - Topographic map. Mule Creek, WY 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1978; 002071
    - Topographic map. Redbird, WY 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1981; 002072
    - Topographic map. Cincinnati East, OH 7.5-min Quad, 1981; 002313
    - Topographic map. Cincinnati West, OH 7.5-min Quad, 1981; 002316
    - Topographic map. Thoroughfare Gap, VA 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1983; 002197
    - Topographic map. Newport, KY 7.5-min Quad, 1987; 002315
    - Topographic map. Addyston, OH - KY 7.5-min Quad, 1987; 002317
    - Topographic map. Guadalupe Peak, TX, 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic. Photocopy., 001608
    - Topographic map. Bowen Flat, WY 7.5 Quad. (1: 24000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 001914
    - Topographic map. La Cima, CA 7.5 min Quad, 002323
    - Topographic map. Garza Peak, CA 7.5 min Quad, 002324
- Locality Information, Series II
  - Africa., 001314
    - Locality information. locality and faunal information: DeDoorns, South Africa., 1929; 000381
    - Locality information. Locality Information; Morocco & Algeria, 1952; 000661
    - Locality information. Locality description: Somalia., 1966; 000208
    - Locality information. locality information; Ordovician Machaeridian, Morocco, Africa, 2007; 000865
    - Locality information. Locality information - Morocco Ordovician (2006-2010), 000922
    - Locality information. Locality information - Morocco Ordovician (2012), 002478
    - Locality information. Locality information (hand drawn map) - Morocco Ordovician (2014), 002484
  - Antartica., 001318
    - Locality information. locality and systematic information, Cretaceous, Antarctica, 2005; 000806
    - Locality information. Locality information, Late Cretaceous Antartica, Seymour Island and Snow Hill Island, 2005; 000813
  - Australia., 001317
    - Locality information. Catalog of localities: Australia., 1962; 000169
  - Canada., 001277
    - Catalog of identifications. Asherman Catalog of Cincinnati Group (Cincinnatian): Schuchert notes on Cincinnatian coll at YPM. 1902, 1927, 000537
    - Catalog of identifications. Catalog of identifications & localities for bryozoa slide collection: North America., 1903; 000004
    - Catalog of identifications. Catalog of ammonite identifications: England, Germany, France., 1905; 000346
    - Catalog of identifications. Bryozoa identifications for published and unpublished material; arranged by box-slide number; master for accn and loc nos., 1905; 000721
    - Catalog of localities. Catalog of localities: Quebec., 1928; 000192
    - Locality information. Locality information for fossil (giant lobster claw) that is questionably similar to the West Haven concretions. Locality information concerns Val Comeau Provincial Park near Tracadie, New Brunswick, Canada., 2002; 002688
    - Locality information. locality information and collectors for George's Bank material off Nova Scotia; The Banquereau., 1910; 000459
    - Locality information. locality information: Manitoba, Canada., 1956; 000441
    - Locality information. Lake Montjoie Area (1: 12000). U.S. Geological Survey: Geologic., 1962; 001594
    - Locality information. Location map of fossil localities: Quebec., 1964; 000164
    - Locality information. Locality information: Nova Scotia, Silurian., 1965; 000491
    - Locality information. Locality information removed from dissertation: British Columbia., 1979; 000356
    - Locality information. Locality information, East coast North America, late Triassic-early Jurassic. exerpts from Field trip guidebook; Gulf, NC - Parrsboro, Nova Scotia [Volume=T351], 1989; 000687
    - Locality information. Locality information: Northwest Territories, Canada., 1995; 000496
    - Locality information. Locality information, Cambrian, British Columbia. 13343, 1998; 000704
    - Locality information. New locality information for old Newfoundland accessions; Ordovician.- Dunbar, Schuchert, Twenhofel., 2003; 000779
    - Locality information. loclity information & unionid clam identifications; Cretaceous; Alberta, Canada, 000810
    - Locality information. St. Jean Stromatoporoids - Locality information and notes, 000957
    - Stratigraphic section. Measured sections: Quebec. 1982, 1983, 000309
  - China., 001280
    - Locality information. Locality information: China, Cambrian., 1982; 000524
  - Czechoslovakia., 001312
    - Stratigraphic section. modern equivalents of Etage Bande system of Barrande in Bohemia, Czechoslovakia; Cambrian, Ordovician, Silurian, Devonian, 000195
  - Denmark. Locality information for Denmark including Greenland., 001308